<?xml version="1.0"?>
<tour>
  <title>Answers</title>
  <screen>
    <title>Community support</title>
    <summary>
      <p>Mailing lists and web forums are traditionally where free
        software projects answer user support questions. However, it can be
        difficult to capture that knowledge and make it available to your
        community.
      </p>
      <p>Launchpad's Answer Tracker makes it easy for users to ask questions
        and stores your community's answers in a searchable knowledge-base.
      </p>
    </summary>
    <screenshot>/+icing/answers-tour-screenshot1.png</screenshot>
    <callout top="" left="">New users can find mailing lists and forums
      intimidating. Launchpad uses a simple guided process to take the pain
      out of asking a support question.
    </callout>
    <callout top="" left="">Launchpad turns previous support requests into a
      knowledge-base for your project. Users can help themselves by searching
      past support questions and answers.
    </callout>
    <callout top="" left="">Launchpad helps your community translate your
      software into hundreds of languages. Localised versions of your
      application are even more useful if users can find support in their own
      language. Launchpad lets people request help and answer support requests
      in their own language. It also filters knowledge-base searches according
      to each user's preferred languages.
    </callout>
    <callout top="" left="">Launchpad helps support teams to organise
      themselves and uses karma to reward people for answering support
      requests. Any individual or team can ask Launchpad to tell them when
      there is a new support request in their language.
    </callout>
  </screen>

  <screen>
    <title>Question detail</title>
    <summary></summary>
    <screenshot>/+icing/answers-tour-screenshot2.png</screenshot>
    <callout top="" left="">Many support requests need discussion before a
      good answer is found. Launchpad helps your community track the
      conversation and offers both web and email interfaces to people who want
      to take part.
    </callout>
    <callout top="" left="">If a long conversation develops around a user
      support request and several possible solutions are suggested, the
      original user can highlight the answer they found most useful.
    </callout>
    <callout top="" left="">Sometimes, a support request arises because of a
      software bug. Your community's support team can generate bug reports
      from support requests. So that everyone can follow the discussion,
      Launchpad links the original support request to the new bug report.
    </callout>
    <transition>
      <p>Thank you for joining us on our tour of Launchpad. If you'd
        like to read more about how Launchpad works, follow our
        <a href="https://help.launchpad.net/FeatureHighlights/">detailed
          feature tour</a>. Or you can talk to us: email
        <a href="mailto:info@launchpad.net">info@launchpad.net</a>.
      </p>
      <p>To try Launchpad for yourself, sign up for your account at <a
        href="https://launchpad.net/+login">https://launchpad.net/+login</a>
      </p>
    </transition>
  </screen>


</tour>