<?xml version="1.0"?>
<tour next="code">
  <title>Launchpad</title>
  <screen>
    <title>Launchpad overview</title>
    <headline>Collaboration and project hosting for free software
        projects
    </headline>
    <summary>
      <p>Collaboration is crucial to free software projects.
          Traditionally, it has been difficult for communities to exchange
          information if they use different tools.
      </p>
      <p>Throughout this tour, you'll see how Launchpad's new approach
          solves the problems of collaboration on software projects. By
          bringing together information from different project-specific
          sources and helping communities to organise themselves into teams,
          Launchpad helps different projects to collaborate on common
          problems, such as bugs in shared code.
      </p>
      <p>Let's start with finding your way around the interface.</p>
    </summary>

    <screenshot>/+icing/launchpad-tour-screenshot1.png</screenshot>
    <callout top="13" left="15">You can always see which project you're
      currently working on in the top-left of the page.
    </callout>
    <callout top="13" left="285">Use the tabs to switch between Launchpad's
      applications.
    </callout>
    <callout top="57" left="100">The Actions menu gives you different options,
      depending on which application you're using.
    </callout>
    <callout top="143" left="28">You can find additional information in the
      expandable boxes below the Actions menu.
    </callout>
  </screen>

  <screen>
    <title>People</title>
    <summary>Launchpad makes it easy to find out what work someone is involved
      in. Each individual's home page shows their team memberships, the
      projects that they're most active in and their contact details.
    </summary>
    <screenshot>/+icing/launchpad-tour-screenshot2.png</screenshot>
    <callout top="53" left="305">Knowing who you're working with is an
      important part of community building and may help you find people to
      collaborate with. Each Launchpad user can post a short description of
      themselves and a photo.
    </callout>
    <callout top="146" left="202">Launchpad shows you which projects a user is
      most active in and the Launchpad applications they've used for those
      projects.
    </callout>
    <callout top="223" left="220">Similarly, you can see all the teams that a
      person has joined.
    </callout>
    <callout top="148" left="369">It's important to be able to contact people
      you want to work with. Launchpad shows you how to contact them and where
      to find a wiki page with more information.
    </callout>
  </screen>

  <screen>
    <title>Teams</title>
    <headline>Spontaneous team creation</headline>
    <summary>
      <p>Strong communities are built on teams. Launchpad helps communities to
        develop rich structures, through the spontaneous creation of teams
        around projects and initiatives.
      </p>
      <p>Anyone can create a team and you can use them just about anywhere
        that you'd use an individual: for example, as a member of another
        team, as a project's bug contact or to access a shared Bazaar branch.
      </p>
    </summary>
    <screenshot>/+icing/launchpad-tour-screenshot3.png</screenshot>
    <callout top="50" left="360">Your team's description is an important way
      to let potential members know what the team plans to do and how it is
      organised.
    </callout>
    <callout top="150" left="220">You can choose from three membership
      policies for your team. Open membership means anyone can join, anyone
      can apply to a moderated team but a team administrator must approve
      their membership and restricted teams are invitation-only.
    </callout>
    <callout top="150" left="430">Teams can own teams and be a member of other
      teams. The row of small icons shows which other teams this team belongs
      to.
    </callout>
  </screen>

  <screen>
    <title>Registering a project</title>
    <summary>Registering your project with Launchpad is the first step to
      improving your collaboration. It's free, quick and easy.
    </summary>
    <screenshot>/+icing/launchpad-tour-screenshot4.png</screenshot>
    <callout>
      Once you've told Launchpad about your project, you're ready to start
      using each of its five tools.
    </callout>
    <callout>Let's start with Code Hosting.</callout>
  </screen>
</tour>
