<?xml version="1.0"?>
<tour next="code">
  <title>Launchpad</title>
  <screen>
    <title>Launchpad overview</title>
    <headline>Collaboration and project hosting for free software
        projects
    </headline>
    <summary>
      <p>Collaboration is crucial to free software projects.
          Traditionally, it has been difficult for communities to exchange
          information if they use different tools.
      </p>
      <p>Throughout this tour, you'll see how Launchpad's new approach
          solves the problems of collaboration on software projects. By
          bringing together information from different project-specific
          sources and helping communities to organise themselves into teams,
          Launchpad helps different projects to collaborate on common
          problems, such as bugs in shared code.
      </p>
      <p>Let's start by finding our way around the interface.</p>
    </summary>

    <screenshot>/+icing/launchpad-tour-screenshot1.png</screenshot>
    <callout top="13" left="15">You can always see which project you're
      currently working on in the top-left of the page.
    </callout>
    <callout top="13" left="285">Use the tabs to switch between Launchpad's
      applications.
    </callout>
    <callout top="57" left="100">The Actions menu is important in Launchpad,
      giving you access to the main functionality of the current application.
    </callout>
    <callout top="143" left="28">You can find additional information in the
      expandable boxes below the Actions menu.
    </callout>
  </screen>

  <screen>
    <title>People</title>
    <summary>Launchpad makes it easy to find out what work someone is involved
      in. Each individual's home page shows their team memberships, the
      projects that they're most active in and their contact details.
    </summary>
    <screenshot>/+icing/launchpad-tour-screenshot2.png</screenshot>
    <callout top="53" left="305">Knowing who you're working with is an
      important part of community building and may help you find people to
      collaborate with.
    </callout>
    <callout top="146" left="202">Launchpad shows you which projects and
      applications each person has used most recently.
    </callout>
    <callout top="223" left="220">You can build a picture of someone's
      interests by seeing which Launchpad teams they've joined.
    </callout>
    <callout top="148" left="369">Launchpad shows you how to contact people
      that you'd like to work with and where to find a wiki page with more
      information.
    </callout>
  </screen>

  <screen>
    <title>Teams</title>
    <headline>Effortless team creation</headline>
    <summary>
      <p>Strong communities are built on teams. Launchpad helps communities to
        develop rich structures, through the effortless creation of teams
        around projects and initiatives.
      </p>
      <p>Teams work just like individuals: they can join other teams and take
        roles in projects, such as acting as a bug supervisor for a project.
      </p>
    </summary>
    <screenshot>/+icing/launchpad-tour-screenshot3.png</screenshot>
    <callout top="50" left="360">Your team's description is an important way
      to let potential members know your plans and how they can join you.
    </callout>
    <callout top="150" left="220">As a team administrator, you choose the
      membership policy that's most appropriate:
      open: anyone can join; moderated: anyone can apply to join but a
      team administrator must approve their membership;
      restricted: a team administrator must invite a person to join.
    </callout>
    <callout top="220" left="390">This row of small icons shows which other
      teams this team has joined.
    </callout>
  </screen>

  <screen>
    <title>Registering a project</title>
    <summary>
      <p>Registering your project with Launchpad is the first step to
        improving your collaboration. It's free, quick and easy.
      </p>
      <p>Once you've told Launchpad about your project, you're ready to
        start using each of its five tools.
      </p>
    </summary>
    <screenshot>/+icing/launchpad-tour-screenshot4.png</screenshot>
    <transition>Let's start with Code Hosting.</transition>
  </screen>
</tour>
