<?xml version="1.0"?>
<tour next="translations">
  <title>Blueprints</title>
  <screen>
    <title>Capturing ideas</title>
    <headline>Capturing and tracking ideas</headline>
    <summary>Launchpad's Blueprint Tracker helps you to manage ideas and
      proposals for your project. A blueprint can be anything from a single
      sentence to a full specification, with information about who is involved
      and where it fits into your project's roadmap.
    </summary>
    <screenshot>/+icing/blueprints-tour-screenshot1.png</screenshot>
    <callout top="" left="">Anyone can create a blueprint for your project,
      helping you to make the most of your community's creativity. As a
      project leader, you set the priority of each blueprint.
    </callout>
    <callout top="" left="">Ideas and proposals within free software projects
      range from an initial concept, through to a full specification. You can
      track how well-defined a blueprint is and the progress of work on its
      implementation.
    </callout>
    <callout top="" left="">You can target blueprints to specific releases of
      your software.
    </callout>
  </screen>
  <screen>
    <title>Blueprint detail</title>
    <screenshot>/+icing/blueprints-tour-screenshot2.png</screenshot>
    <callout top="" left="">At a glance, you can see who is involved in the
      blueprint, its current status and any meetings at which it has been
      discussed.
    </callout>
    <callout top="" left="">By telling Launchpad where a blueprint fits into
      your project, and what other blueprints must be completed first, you can
      create a roadmap for your software.
    </callout>
    <callout top="" left="">If a blueprint arises from a bug report, or a
      branch of code implements a blueprint, you can link them enabling
      everyone to see how they relate.
    </callout>
  </screen>

  <screen>
    <title>Planning meetings</title>
    <summary>
      <p>Many software projects find that face to face team meetings
        are an invaluable way to build community and to work together on
        specific goals.
      </p>
      <p>Launchpad makes it easy for anyone in the community to organise
        meetings and development sprints. Each meeting's agenda consists of
        blueprints. Anyone can suggest a blueprint for discussion, while you
        approve each proposal.
      </p>
    </summary>
    <screenshot>/+icing/blueprints-tour-screenshot3.png</screenshot>
    <transition>For the final stop on our tour, let's look at how Launchpad
      helps your community to answer user support questions.
    </transition>
  </screen>

</tour>