<?xml version="1.0"?>
<tour next="answers">
  <title>Translations</title>
  <screen>
    <title>Translation for everyone</title>
    <summary>Translators shouldn't have to be coders. Launchpad's simple web
      interface makes it easy for anyone to translate software into their own
      language.
    </summary>
    <screenshot>/+icing/translations-tour-screenshot1.png</screenshot>
    <callout top="" left="">New contributors want to know where their work is
      needed. Launchpad gives an overview of the translation status of each
      application: purple, green and blue represent translated strings, red is
      untranslated.
    </callout>
  </screen>
  <screen>
    <title>Automation and organisation</title>
    <headline>Automating and organising translations</headline>
    <summary>Launchpad helps you share the work of translating your software,
      both within your own community and with other communities.
    </summary>
    <screenshot>/+icing/translations-tour-screenshot2.png</screenshot>
    <transition>
      <p>Maintaining the quality of your translations is
        vital. Balancing quality with low barriers to entry can be difficult.
        Launchpad offers you three translation policies, from fully open to
        restricted.
      </p>
      <p>If you choose a fully open policy, anyone can make
        a translation and anyone can review a translation. Alternatively, you
        can appoint individuals or teams as trusted translators for each
        language.
      </p>
      <p>Common phrases reoccur in the interfaces of many
        applications. When you're translating a string, Launchpad finds other
        places where it has already been translated and tells you how it
        appears there. You're free to accept Launchpad's suggestion or to
        enter your own translation.
      </p>
      <p >When you begin work on a new release of your
        software, translators should be free to continue work on previous
        releases. With Launchpad, you can maintain separate translation
        efforts for each release.
      </p>
    </transition>
  </screen>

</tour>