<?xml version="1.0"?>
<tour next="blueprints">
  <title>Bugs</title>

  <screen>
    <title>Multi-project bugs</title>
    <summary>Launchpad's bug tracker is unique. It helps you track the status
      of the same bug as it affects multiple projects and to work with those
      projects to find a solution.
    </summary>
    <screenshot>/+icing/bugs-tour-screenshot1.png</screenshot>
    <callout>Launchpad knows about four occurrences of this bug and tracks its
      status in each community. Those communities that use Launchpad's bug
      tracker share this single bug report, with a common comment history and
      bug number.
    </callout>
    <callout>Launchpad's openoffice.org (Ubuntu) community use Launchpad's bug
      tracker directly. They have assigned Matthias Klose to take
      responsibility for solving the bug as it affects them.

      The upstream OpenOffice.org community and Debian's neon26 team
      use external bug trackers. Launchpad tracks the status of the bug in
      their trackers but also links to their bug reports, making it easy to
      follow the detail of their progress.
    </callout>
    <callout>If you discover another community affected by this bug, it's easy
      to include them in the conversation.
    </callout>
  </screen>

  <screen>
    <title>Discussing bugs</title>
    <summary>Anyone who is interested can participate in the discussion of a
      bug. Launchpad's bug tracker offers both web and email interfaces,
      making it ideal for both newer users and experienced
      developers.
    </summary>
    <screenshot>/+icing/bugs-tour-screenshot2.png</screenshot>
    <callout>You can attach files - such as screen shots and logs - to help
      bug triagers understand the cause of a bug.
    </callout>
    <callout>Subscribing to a bug lets you follow its progress by email.
      Launchpad users and teams can choose to subscribe to a bug, while a
      project's bug contact is automatically notified of new bug reports and
      changes to existing bugs.
    </callout>
    <transition>In some projects, bug reports are used to request new
      features. Let's look at Launchpad's Blueprint Tracker, which helps you
      track and develop ideas for your software.
    </transition>
  </screen>
</tour>