<?xml version="1.0"?>
<tour next="bugs">
  <title>Code</title>
  <screen>
    <title>Code hosting</title>
    <summary><p>Bazaar version control lets anyone create their own branch of
      your project's code.
      </p>
      <p>Launchpad helps you keep track of all the branches of your code. It
        can even continuously import most CVS and Subversion repositories,
        giving you a Bazaar branch of the code.
      </p>
      <p>First, you need to tell Launchpad about your code.
      </p>
    </summary>
    <screenshot>/+icing/code-tour-screenshot1.png</screenshot>
    <callout>If your code is already in a Bazaar branch, simply give Launchpad
      its URL and a short summary.
    </callout>
    <callout>You can use Bazaar to access code stored in Subversion and CVS
      repositories by requesting that Launchpad make the code available in
      Bazaar. Launchpad will regularly update the Bazaar branch from the
      original repository.
    </callout>
  </screen>
  <screen>
    <title>Browsing branches</title>
    <summary>Browsing all the branches associated with your project is easy.
      Launchpad catalogues each branch, including its full revision history,
      and displays major project branches alongside those created by
      individuals.
    </summary>
    <screenshot>/+icing/code-tour-screenshot2.png</screenshot>
    <callout>Launchpad Code Hosting integrates with Launchpad's other
      applications. If a branch fixes a bug or implements a blueprint,
      Launchpad links the two.
    </callout>
    <callout>Both teams and individuals can register their branches of your
      code, helping you to find all lines of development associated with your
      project.
    </callout>
    <callout>Each branch's owner can set the status of their branch. This
      status and the branch description help new developers choose which line
      of development to branch.
    </callout>
    <transition>Let's take a look at one of the branches in detail.
    </transition>
  </screen>
  <screen>
    <title>Branch detail</title>
    <summary>Launchpad shows you the detail of each branch it knows
      about.
    </summary>
    <screenshot>/+icing/code-tour-screenshot3.png</screenshot>
    <callout>The branch owner's image appears beside the branch name, in the
      top-left corner of the page. This makes it easy to identify the
      individual or team responsible for the branch.
    </callout>
    <callout>Launchpad shows you where the branch is hosted, making it easy to
      retrieve the code.
    </callout>
    <callout>Launchpad shows you the latest activity in this branch by
      displaying the most recent developer commit messages.
    </callout>
    <callout>For more detail, you can browse the code itself, with diffs and a
      complete revision history.
    </callout>
    <transition>Next, let's look at how you can use Launchpad to manage bugs.
    </transition>
  </screen>
</tour>