<?xml version="1.0"?>
<tour next="blueprints">
  <title>Bugs</title>
  <screen>
    <title>Searching for bugs</title>
    <summary>Anyone can search, view and comment on tens of thousands of
      bugs filed in Launchpad.
    </summary>
    <screenshot>/+icing/bugs-tour-screenshot1.png</screenshot>
    <callout top="45" left="320">Search bugs filed against hundreds of
      projects and packages.
    </callout>
    <callout top="110" left="90">Get a snapshot of issues currently affecting
      Launchpad communities.
    </callout>
    <callout top="110" left="290">And see which issues have recently been
      solved.
    </callout>
  </screen>

  <screen>
    <title>Viewing a bug</title>
    <summary>Individual bug pages show how a bug affects other communities,
      who is working on the bug and what discussion has taken place.
    </summary>
    <screenshot>/+icing/bugs-tour-screenshot2.png</screenshot>
    <callout top="86" left="280">You can track a bug's status across different
      communities, even if they use external bug trackers.
    </callout>
    <callout top="117" left="450">See which individual or team each community
      has assigned to work on a bug. Or link to the bug in an external
      tracker.
    </callout>
    <callout top="237" left="440">If other projects or distributions are
      affected by this bug, sharing it with them takes just a few clicks.
    </callout>
    <callout top="214" left="72">Any Launchpad user or team can subscribe to
      a bug, giving them email notification of status changes and new
      comments.
    </callout>
  </screen>

  <screen>
    <title>Listing project bugs</title>
    <screenshot>/+icing/bugs-tour-screenshot3.png</screenshot>
    <summary>A project's bug listing gives a quick overview of how many issues
      are outstanding.
    </summary>
    <callout top="113" left="122">Coloured bug icons make it easy to see how
      important the project considers each bug to be.
    </callout>
    <callout top="152" left="307">A yellow Bazaar icon shows that a bug is
      linked to a branch of code that is intended to fix it.
    </callout>
    <callout top="172" left="74">Tags help communities spontaneously
      categorise their bugs.
    </callout>
  </screen>

  <screen>
    <title>Assigning a bug</title>
    <screenshot>/+icing/bugs-tour-screenshot4.png</screenshot>
    <summary>Launchpad makes it easy to keep bug reports up to date.</summary>

    <callout top="44" left="118">Each community affected by a bug can choose
      their own assignee and status, but all communities share the same
      comment history.
    </callout>
    <callout top="145" left="70">Quick-links to that community's bug contact
      and the current user, speed up bug assignment.
    </callout>
  </screen>

  <screen>
    <title>Commenting on a bug</title>Commenting on a bug
    <screenshot>/+icing/bugs-tour-screenshot5.png</screenshot>
    <summary>Shared comment histories helps communities solve common bugs.</summary>

    <callout top="0" left="356">Bug comments can have subjects, to make long
      comment histories easier to scan.
    </callout>
    <callout top="23" left="185">Attachments - such as screen shots, code
      patches or logs - make comments much more useful.
    </callout>
  </screen>

</tour>