<?xml version="1.0"?>
<tour next="bugs">
  <title>Code</title>
  <screen>
    <title>Code hosting</title>
    <summary><p>Bazaar version control lets anyone create their own branch of
      your project's code.
      </p>
      <p>Launchpad helps you keep track of all the branches of your code. It
        can even continuously import most CVS and Subversion repositories,
        giving you a Bazaar branch of the code.
      </p>
      <p>First, you need to tell Launchpad about your code.
      </p>
    </summary>
    <screenshot>/+icing/code-tour-screenshot1.png</screenshot>
    <callout>If your code is in a Bazaar branch, simply give Launchpad its URL
      and a short summary.
    </callout>
    <callout>If you want to use Bazaar to access code in a Subversion or CVS
      repository, you can request an import.
    </callout>
  </screen>
  <screen>
    <title>Browsing branches</title>
    <summary>Browsing all the branches associated with your project is easy.
      Launchpad catalogues each branch, including its full revision history,
      and displays major project branches alongside those created by
      individuals.
    </summary>
    <screenshot>/+icing/code-tour-screenshot2.png</screenshot>
    <callout>Here the trunk branch is owned by Bazaar Developers, a Launchpad
      team. Launchpad team branches work like Subversion repositories: they're
      hosted centrally and only members of that team have commit access. The
      other branches shown here have been registered by individual developers.
    </callout>
    <callout>Launchpad Code Hosting integrates with Launchpad's other
      applications. If a branch fixes a bug or implements a blueprint,
      Launchpad links the two.
    </callout>
    <callout>Each branch's owner can set the status of their branch. This
      status and the branch description help new developers choose which line
      of development to branch.
    </callout>
    <transition>Let's take a look at one of the branches in detail.
    </transition>
  </screen>
  <screen>
    <title>Branch detail</title>
    <summary>Launchpad shows you the detail of each branch it knows
      about.
    </summary>
    <screenshot>/+icing/code-tour-screenshot3.png</screenshot>
    <callout>The branch owner's image appears beside the branch name, in the
      top-left corner of the page. This makes it easy to identify the
      individual or team responsible for the branch.
    </callout>
    <callout>Launchpad shows you where the branch is hosted, making it easy to
      branch.
    </callout>
    <callout>Details of the branch's most recent revisions, complete with the
      developer's commit messages, give you a flavour of this line of
      development.
    </callout>
    <callout>For more detail, you can browse the code itself, with complete
      revision history and diffs.
    </callout>
    <transition>Next, let's look at how you can use Launchpad to manage bugs
      and collaborate with other projects you share code with.
    </transition>
  </screen>
</tour>